{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"145/47",
			"answer":"145/47",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"391/30",
			"answer":"391/30",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"784/60",
			"answer":"784/60",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"644/46",
			"answer":"644/46",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"978/97",
			"answer":"978/97",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"276/25",
			"answer":"276/25",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"760/95",
			"answer":"760/95",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"642/16",
			"answer":"642/16",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"556/25",
			"answer":"556/25",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"193/12",
			"answer":"193/12",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}

	]
}